1. openBrowser(AppUrl)
5. navigateToUrl(AppUrl)
9. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/VerifiedUserRatingUnverified/Page_theworklife - Find Great People To Work With/input_Forgot password_username"), "vijayvstest01@gmail.com")
13. setEncryptedText(findTestObject("Object Repository/VerifiedUserRatingUnverified/Page_theworklife - Find Great People To Work With/input_Forgot password_password"), "cvW8qx4B2o3F4VwP/kNsqA==")
17. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/VerifiedUserRatingUnverified/Page_theworklife - Find Great People To Work With/button_Sign in"))
21. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/VerifiedUserRatingUnverified/Page_Home/input_View all_searchText"), "User User")
25. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/VerifiedUserRatingUnverified/Page_Home/button_No search results_btnSearch"))
29. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/VerifiedUserRatingUnverified/Page_Search/div_user user"))
33. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/VerifiedUserRatingUnverified/Page_View Profile/button_Rate Now"))
37. delay(5)
41. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/VerifiedUserRatingUnverified/Page_View Profile/p_This is an unverified user Please input Facebook or LinkedIn Profile Link for user user"), "This is an unverified user. Please input Facebook or LinkedIn Profile Link for user user.")
45. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/VerifiedUserRatingUnverified/Page_View Profile/button_Cancel"))
49. closeBrowser()
1. closeBrowser()