1. openBrowser("")
5. navigateToUrl("https://qa.thework.life/")
9. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Incorrect SMN FB/Page_theworklife - Find Great People To Work With/a_Join Now"))
13. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Incorrect SMN FB/Page_theworklife - Find Great People To Work With/button_Facebook"))
17. switchToWindowTitle("Facebook")
21. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Incorrect SMN FB/Page_Facebook/input_Email address or phone number_email"), "an@ksfks.com")
25. setEncryptedText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Incorrect SMN FB/Page_Facebook/input_Password_pass"), "FIyHSpwHMz/RrAsWal25wQ==")
29. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Incorrect SMN FB/Page_Facebook/input_Password_login"))
33. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Incorrect SMN FB/Page_Facebook/div_Incorrect email addressThe email address that youve entered doesnt match any account Sign up for an account"))
37. verifyTextPresent("Incorrect email address", false)
41. closeBrowser()
1. closeBrowser()