1. openBrowser("")
5. navigateToUrl("https://qa.thework.life/")
9. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Rate/Page_theworklife - Find Great People To Work With/input_Forgot password_username"), "worklifetest10001@gmail.com")
13. setEncryptedText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Rate/Page_theworklife - Find Great People To Work With/input_Forgot password_password"), "x8UobeF0bbxd7GrPsdhkIlsTrhBxwBw1")
17. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Rate/Page_theworklife - Find Great People To Work With/button_Sign in"))
21. setEncryptedText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Rate/Page_theworklife - Find Great People To Work With/input_Password does not match_password"), "XU9cBalmEBp1UP+jEU2w4UUBUuNgBY4U")
25. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Rate/Page_theworklife - Find Great People To Work With/button_Sign in"))
29. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Rate/Page_Home/input_View all_searchText"), "vijay")
33. click(findTestObject("Search user/Search user button"))
37. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Rate/Page_Search/div_Vijay Test"))
41. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Rate/Page_View Profile/button_Rate Now"))
45. waitForElementClickable(findTestObject("Rate/Page_View Profile/span_Desire to work with again_star3"), 3)
49. sleep(10000)
53. delay(5)
57. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Rate/Page_View Profile/span_Desire to work with again_star3"))
61. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Rate/Page_View Profile/span_Encourages work life balance_star3"))
65. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Rate/Page_View Profile/span_Dependability_star3"))
69. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Rate/Page_View Profile/span_Solution Seeker_star3"))
73. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Rate/Page_View Profile/span_Willingness to Learn_star3"))
77. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Rate/Page_View Profile/span_Enthusiasm_star3"))
81. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Rate/Page_View Profile/span_Clarity in Communication_star3"))
85. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Rate/Page_View Profile/span_Mutual Respect_star3"))
89. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Rate/Page_View Profile/button_Next"))
93. waitForElementClickable(findTestObject("Rate/Page_View Profile/textarea_test recomendation test on qa enviornment for vijay test account"), 3)
97. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Rate/Page_View Profile/textarea_test recomendation test on qa enviornment for vijay test account"), "test recomendation test on qa enviornment for vijay test account tst test test test for recommendation test scenario vijay test")
101. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Rate/Page_View Profile/button_Submit"))
105. waitForElementClickable(findTestObject("Rate/Page_View Profile/a_OK"), 3)
109. delay(5)
113. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Rate/Page_View Profile/a_OK"))
117. closeBrowser()
1. closeBrowser()